What have you got there ?
God !
Baxter ?
He got our dog !
He got Baxter !
Shut up , Norman .
Can this happen to a normal woman ?
Baxter 's fertilizer .
And everyone 's just standing there like
staring .
Why don 't they just catch that thing ?
How hard could it be in a place full of dead ends ?
Fuck !
Wrists are for girls ...
I 'm slitting my throat .
You should definitely hang .
Maybe even your final moment is a cliché around here .
Not ours .
B , ours will rock .
You don 't think our deaths should be a little more than cheap entertainment ?
You jazzed me on this . Don 't wuss out now .
It 's the idea of everyone staring at me just lying there .
I mean , what if they just ... laugh ?
They 'll be in awe .
B , suicide is like the ultimate " fuck you " .
Come on it 's so us .
It 's the pact .
See , it 's easy for you . You don 't care .
We swore we 'd go together , one way or another .
- When we were eight . - So ?
Out by sixteen or dead in this scene , but together forever .
Together forever .
United against life as we know it .
Us dead will be the shit , B. Trust me .
Too much blood .
- And I can see your gonch ! - Just do it .
All right , all right ... uh .
Well that was completely
disturbing , wasn 't it ?
You know , the Fitzgerald sisters clearly worked very ...
God !
I mean I , I ...
I am completely sickened .
Sickened ... by that , wasn 't I ?
Look , see me in the guidance office , after class , you two , separately .
Can we see the ones of Ginger again ?
Enough !
Hey !
Life in Bailey Downs , huh ?
Who 's next ?
Oh yes , ladies , run . Run for daddy !
Bounce .
I bet she 's good to go .
- You wanna do a Fitzgerald ? - You 're kidding ?
Not the little dweeb , you goinks . The one with the rack !
The redhead .
Odd .
I think McCardy just checked me .
Like you care , right ?
High school is just a mindless little breeders machine .
A total hormonal toilet .
I 'd rather wait it all out in our room .
- What is with your back ? - I don 't know .
Hey , ' Search and Destroy ' . Go .
OK , Trina Sinclair .
Excellent selection . Continue .
Trina Sinclair , D.0.A. at the hair dye aisle .
Perished while seeking matching barrettes on nothing but diet pills and laxatives .
Likes her shorts stuck up her ass crack .
Favorite homework excuse : my nail glitter ate it .
Basic pleasure model .
Your standard , cumbuckety date bait .
Good one .
- Line change . Let 's go , girls . - Fucking Bitch !
Uh oh .
Let 's do this again .
We 'll try it over Sara , thanks .
I 'll cover you .
Good .
Bounce , babies , bounce ! Keep running .
You want it baby .
C 'mon , honey !
oh yeah , baby !
- You want it , baby . - Fuck off !
'The Beast of Bailey Downs ' strikes again .
That 's four dogs this week .
Oh ! Wow ... Bonus !
I guess you 're D.O.A. on a dog . Huh , Fitz-face ?
That 's enough .
- Are you OK ? - Terrific .
That is one mother-fucking mad dog .
Brigitte , go get cleaned up .
Don 't ever touch my sister again .
Stop me , freak .
Enough ! Break it up !
Hey , that janitor was looking right down your shirt .
Sure .
Want me to kill her ? I 'll kill her for you , B.
Whatever .
No , not whatever . This isn 't whatever .
Seriously , what about torture ?
Anything you want .
Or ... she has that dog .
We could kidnap it , make it look like he got eaten by ' The Beast of Bailey Downs ' .
We got all that blood and fake guts from the slide show .
Yeah , that 's wicked . Let 's do it .
Hi Sam , how are you ?
She screws a drug dealer ; she 's begging for negative attention .
So , Sam are you ... are you gonna call me ?
OK , you have my number , right ?
Remember when I gave it to you , before ?
Sam .
OK , bye ...
Let 's go .
Such a dickhead .
See ...
You 'd let idiots get away with fucking you up .
That 's why the big Buddha made me .
To stop them .
Yeah , so far you 're really kicking ass .
Just give me one clean shot . Just one , I fucking promise you .
- Don 't humor me ! - So , Fitz ...
I think we should get together .
No .
Bitch !
Jump , Norman . Come on .
B ...
Just say you won 't go average on me .
Just ' cause some gonad gets his zipper going ?
Rather be dead .
- I 'd rather die than be here without you . - Relax , you 're not , you big suck .
Ginger , don 't push your sister .
God , I hate our gene pool .
Look , girls .
Come on . Let go . Let go . You 're ruining it !
Ginger , why are you rubbing your back ?
- It hurts . - Why ?
Well , pain flows up your nerve endings to the synapses in your brain ...
She 's not funny .
- How did you hurt it ? - Being dead .
Does it hurt down by your tail bone , or is it up higher ?
- Is it tight throughout here ? - Maybe .
Does it ache back here ?
- Might ... - Oh my god .
Do you think it 's cramps ?
Give it a rest ... for two seconds ?
Pam , we 're eating .
Henry , the girls are both three years late menstruating . OK ?
It 's not normal . If it 's finally happening ...
It 's not !
Honey , it 's nothing to be scared of . It 's the most normal thing in the world .
- Maybe it 's cancer of the spine . - Ginger-Ann ...
Or tuberculosis .
- See what your attitude does ? - Or spondylitis .
- Spondo ... what ? - Fuses your vertebrae together .
- Nice . - Brigitte , stop it .
Have a fit !
I 've had just about enough of that tone .
- That makes two of us . Fuck ! - That 's it . To your room !
Gladly .
Brigitte , you are not connected at her wrist .
Your father and I have counseling tonight . I don 't want you leaving the house .
The news says there 's still some wild animal on the loose .
They never go out .
Well , you 're a big help .
As usual .
- Ginger . - What ?
- We 'll get caught . - No , we won 't .
- The dog won 't even be out . - He has to pee some time .
People don 't leave their dogs out alone anymore .
Then you will just have to distract her
while I nab the pooch and make with the gore .
- I can 't distract her . - The fuck , B. This is your idea .
If you don 't like your ideas , stop having them .
Sorry .
I 've just just had it with eating all their shit , OK ?
Check it out .
Now we can even leave a body . She 'll freak .
Oh , wicked .
Take his
leg ?
He 's still warm .
Oh , gross .
Shit !
Leave it then . The drag .
You got some on you .
Nice .
What ?
B ,
I just got the curse .
Eww .
Well , it 's not contagious !
I know that .
God !
I mean , kill yourself to be different and your own body screws you .
But if I start simping around tampon dispensers
and moaning about PMS , shoot me , OK ?
Let 's get out of here .
Ginger ?
Ginger !
Oh God . He 's right behind me .
Oh , my God !
Ginger !
Get up . Come on , get up !
Oh , fuck me .
Shit !
Mom !
Dad ! Help !
Let me see .
- No , it hurts , it burns ... - I have to see it , Ginger .
- What was it ? What was it ? - I don 't know . A big dog , maybe .
That 's not ... What did I do ? What ...
Shh .
I saw this thing once , on bears .
Said a bear will like , come after a girl on the rag , because of the smell .
It wasn 't a fucking bear !
There wasn 't any fucking bears anywhere near here .
- Does that hurt ? - No .
That 's impossible . They 're already healing .
No , this isn 't right . I 'm calling 911 .
No ! No !
B , I 'm not bleeding anymore . Right ?
I mean ... just
spare me Pam finding out .
OK ? I 'm OK . OK ?
- OK . - I 'm OK .
- I thought you were gonna die . - I 'm OK .
Preying upon normal healthy cells ,
the intruder gradually devours the host from within .
Eventually the invader consumes its host completely ,
and finally destroys it .
Complete meiosis involves two successive division sequences ,
which result in four new cells , each of which is haploid .
This one comes with a free calendar .
Are you sure it 's just cramps ?
Just so you know
the words ' just ' and ' cramps ' , they don 't go together .
OK , you 're really girling out here .
One day , you too will know my pain .
Hey , diss me or whatever , but I got three sisters
and nothing quite takes the edge off like a good toke .
Well , maybe I like my edge , thanks .
Or maybe you 're just chicken to lose it .
Just pass it , fag .
- That a girl . - Yeah .
An eighth 's fifty .
- I don 't want any drugs . - Then amscray .
I was just wondering what you hit .
Well , officer , it looked like a lycanthrope to me , sir .
- I know what a lycanthrope is . - Sure you do .
Think you see werewolves a lot ?
'MW , do you ' ?
Is it working ?
No ... but now I just don 't care .
What the hell are you guys doing in here ?
Sam , the Man .
Sam , man , we just needed a place to come and smoke .
Hey , you know , I have an idea .
Why don 't you guys get the fuck out of my van , assholes !
No I 'm serious . Get out !
Get out . Get out !
- Samuel , what happened to your truck ? - I tapped a tree , all right . Good bye .
Ginge , lets go .
Yeah , why don 't you stick to your own species Fitzenstein ?
Trina , stick my fist .
Oh you bitch ! It 's OK , baby .
Ginge , what 's going on ?
Something 's wrong .
Like more than you being just
female .
Can you just say something , please ?
Woah !
'Woah ' ? That 's it ? ' Woah ' ?
I can 't have a hairy chest , B. That 's fucked !
No way .
The fuck ? What the fuck ?
- This isn 't ... - What ?
- No way , like ... - What ?
Bitten on a full moon . Now you 're hairy ?
I know , but think about it .
Well thank you for taking my total fucking nightmare so seriously !
Oh shit !
What if I 'm dying or something ?
We gotta see the nurse .
I 'm sure it seems like a lot of blood . It 's a period .
But really it was like a ...
geyser .
Everyone seems to panic their first time .
Neither of you have had a period before and you 're how old ?
I 'm almost 16 , she just turned 15 . She skipped a grade .
A thick , syrupy , voluminous discharge is not uncommon .
The bulk of the uterine lining is shed within the first few days .
Contractions , cramps , squeeze it out like a pump .
In three to five days you 'll find lighter , bright-red bleeding .
That may turn to a brownish or blackish sludge , which signals the end of the flow .
- OK , so it 's all normal ? - Very !
Expect it every twenty eight days , give or take , for the next thirty years .
Great . Thanks .
What about hair that wasn 't there before , and pain ?
Mhm , comes with the territory .
Well , thank you . Lets go , B.
Wait , you 'll have to protect against both pregnancy and STDs now ...
Play safe !
Wish these where babies ' legs .
Ginger 's very favorite .
Congratulations sweetie . You know you can ask me anything .
You 're so dead .
I didn 't .
Our little girl 's a young woman now .
- I 'd never tell her anything . - Unless you wanted to piss me off !
- I want you to be OK . - I am ! I just got my period , OK ?
Now , I 've got weird hairs , so what ? That means I 've got hormones ,
and they may make me butt-ugly , but they do not make me a monster .
So you got bit by a great big hormone .
Well not by what you think . They don 't exist !
Norman , shut the fuck up !
Maybe he 's barking at you .
Did I change last night ?
Howl at the moon , kill shit and change back this morning ?
Huh ? No !
Did it take a silver bullet to stop that thing ? No !
It got killed by a fucking truck .
You always blow off anything you don 't get .
Yeah , when it 's bullshit !
You 're doing drugs with guys . Something is definitely wrong with you .
You know , maybe you 're right . Maybe I do see a monster .
Yeah , it 's got these little green eyes .
Oh yeah , like I really wish I was hemorrhaging and hairy ,
and sucking off Jason McCardy .
- Well you always wanted to be me ! - Well this isn 't you , so .
Oh , poor B.
I 'm growing up and obviously you 're not , huh ?
Well don 't let me hold you back or anything .
Oh well , don 't worry , I won 't .
Only one creature on earth destroys for pure pleasure .
It 's a werewolf .
Oh my god , there it is .
It 's hideous !
Get the fuck outta the bathroom ! I 'm trying to get ready !
Ginger ? Oh my god .
( whistles ) Oh babe ...
Check it out .
Not as good as that .
Hello , hello , hello ...
Hey !
Kid , you got a smoke ?
No .
You got a light then ?
Oh , thank you .
I just spent a week of my life looking for you .
You can give me a second
You dropped this - in my truck .
OK , we both saw it . What the fuck was it ?
- It 's what you hit . - Hmm ! I know ,
but what the fuck was it ?
See , I flattened an animal . Furry , all-fours , could be anything .
But here I am , thinking ' lycanthrope ' .
That 's crazy , huh ?
Book me into the rubber motel , I 'm officially all fucked up , right ?
What if you 're not ?
Well , that would explain the human circumcised dick ,
and why you were running for your life from it .
I have to go . Thanks for my stuff .
What 's your name ?
- Bullshit . - Thanks .
No , hey , bullshit ?
What do you say ?
Swear you won 't call a freak show .
Yeah , I swear .
I 'm changing , like right now and full moons have nothing to do with it .
You 're serious ?
And everything I look at goes silver bullet ,
in a gun , to my head , the end .
Wow .
Let 's not panic here . I mean
for one , that thing on the road , my van did a pretty good job on it ,
without the benefit of silver bullets . So , let 's just forget the Hollywood rules .
There 's got to be a cure , right ?
Otherwise , there would be a hell of a lot more of them .
It 's like an infection , it works from the inside out . It 's like a virus .
Biology , there 's something you can sink your teeth into .
So to speak .
You 're real , your problem 's real , the solution 's real .
Not bam , death by morality call .
Then again when I started piercing shit , I got infections ,
girl says try pure silver , cleared up like that .
The ancients thought pure metals purified their blood .
- They thought leeches did , too . - They do .
Hey , why don 't you get your slut-bitch sister a leash ?
What a freak .
Nice bird necklace .
Ginger , a word ?
- Is it sorry ? - No .
Come on Jason , let 's go .
Oh yes .
Ginger !
Hey . She 's ovulating !
See you , freak . Bye bye .
This is a very exciting , confusing time for your sister .
Boys , her body , trying to fit in .
Maybe if she felt that she could share more with you ,
you 'd both be a lot happier .
You know , Brigitte , your turn 's coming , too ... one clay .
My stomach .
Hey , take it easy , all right ? We 've got all night .
Sorry , you just taste really good .
- Just lie back and relax . - You lie back and relax !
Who 's the guy here ?
Who 's the guy here ? Huh ? Who 's the fucking guy here ?
Don 't we need protection here ?
Stop it !
Wait a second !
You 're fucking hilarious , cave boy .
Ginge ?
What happened ?
Did he hurt you ?
If he hurt you , you should tell .
Oh , my god !
- Get out ! Get out ! - What happened ?
Something is really , really wrong with me , B.
What happened ?
I get this ache and
I thought it was for sex , but it 's to tear everything into fucking pieces .
Where is he ?
Next door .
Oh , my god !
You killed Norman .
He barked and he barked and he kept fucking barking , and ...
I just ... I just
I couldn 't stop myself .
B , what am I supposed to do ?
It wasn 't at all like I thought it would be .
There was just all this squirming and squealing .
And than he 's done , and you 're like ' Oh ? '
Just probably out there telling everyone what a freak I am .
We 'll say the same thing about him .
It doesn 't work like that . I mean , he got laid .
I 'm just a lay .
He 's a hero and I 'm just a lay , a freak mutant lay .
Did you use something ?
No .
You really think this will work ?
We have to try something .
Where did you get that , that ring ?
I found it .
Too bad .
You should have one too . I mean , for being with me on this .
Ready ?
Yeah .
Shit , it 's stuck !
Hold still .
- Fuck ! Hurry up ! - Sorry , sorry .
It 's almost there .
How do you feel ?
Wicked .
Norman ?
Here , Norman .
Hurry up !
- Hold still . - I am , hurry up .
- Oh yea . - Oh yes .
Come on , hit it , baby .
- Nice . - Alright .
- Oh , McCardy what happened to you ? - Ginger Fitzgerald rocked my world .
Whoa shit !
What , did you get your rag , too ?
Oh , shit !
It must be ink , all right ? Fuck !
Hi !
Brigitte !
Brigitte , come here .
What the fuck , B ? Did you get a boyfriend or something ?
No , we just ...
I 'll be right back .
Oh my god .
Hey , what 's up ? Look , if silver 's shot , I 've been reading and I got another idea .
Are you on drugs , like right now ? I 'm in class here .
Yeah , excuse me for giving a shit .
- I 'll come see you later , OK ? - Whatever .
The Fitzen sisters are really getting around .
- OK , line change . Lets go . - He thinks I got bit .
I trust you , and you blab to the first fuck-up that comes along .
He knows stuff , he wants to help .
He wants to get down your pants , stupid !
So , sluts run in the family ... quel shocker !
You 're fucking dead .
Oh yea .
- Knock it off ! - Ginger , no !
Ginger , no ! Stop !
Fight , fight , fight ...
- You started it . - Ginger , to the office .
This school has a 'zero tolerance for violence ' policy .
I mean a temper like that is inexcusable
barring substantial extenuating circumstances .
What are you looking at ? Huh ? My pen exploded , OK . My red pen .
That was fucking incredible .
Get your camera , don 't you have your camera ?
This is wall-worthy . Come on .
You gave it to Jason .
You had unprotected sex , and you infected him .
OOps !
- I have to see Sam . He 's got an idea . - I 'll bet he does . Well , let 's go .
If you come , you can 't be weird , Ginger .
If he gets I lied . If he gets that you 're really the one who 's really ...
a what ? ... a monster ? Huh , a freak ?
If he thinks I dicked him around , he 'll blow this off .
I 'll behave .
Romeo , Romeo , wherefore art thou Romeo ?
. Hey' . Hey'
Sorry about before . I was just afraid someone would hear us , that 's all .
Yeah , she is just a little moody lately .
That whole silver thing didn 't quite work out , did it ?
I wasn 't expecting company .
My sister , Ginger . She knows .
If you two come in here , you see sweet fuck all . Understood ?
Jesus !
Wicked ! Smoke us up !
Yeah , wicked huh ? Get the fuck out !
All right , Brigitte , it breaks down like this .
I compared homeopathic treatments of infections
to the folklore of all this . Take a look .
Aconitum di lycoctonum .
- ' Lyco ' as in wolf ? - Right .
It 's called Monkshood .
It 's a cousin of wolfsbane , except this stuff is safe in small doses .
It 's a super oxidant breed , radical detox .
It promotes white blood cell growth .
Which fight infection . Do you have some ?
Well , it 's perennial .
It grows everywhere , but only in the spring .
Fuck ! This is bullshit , OK ?
- I seeded some , I 'm growing it . - She doesn 't have time for that .
She 's killed a dog already . She 's fucked .
She 's growing a tail . Did you tell him that ?
Ginger !
You 're growing a tail ?
Yes .
Look , he 's just another wank job . OK ?
What the fuck do you think you are ? Give me that .
What the fuck are you ? Pervert , she 's 15 !
Ginger , wait outside !
Fine , if he rapes you , don 't come crying .
I 'll be at home .
She 's just freaking .
I do not think of you that way .
Fuck !
Fuck ! Fuck !
Your dad 's battery is dead again . He 's stranded at the supermarket .
- Wanna go for a ride ? - Jesus , can 't you knock ?
Don 't you ' Jesus ' me .
You don 't have anything I haven 't seen before .
That 's what you think .
What is that supposed to mean ?
Nothing , I 'm just , I 'm fat , all right . Get out !
Ginger , you are not fat .
These fashion models are all on speed to look like that .
Get out !
OK . Gosh .
I 'll be back soon .
Give me back my dog .
- Trina , I don 't have your dog . - Ginger took him . I saw her .
You know , I feel sorry for you . He doesn 't like you .
He 's a cherry-hound . He 's into virgins .
Trina , you 're bleeding . Go home .
If you are so fucking smart , you won 't give him the satisfaction .
Somebody just once shouldn 't give that fucker the satisfaction !
- Trina , go now . - You are as big a cunt as your sister .
I am not .
- Hey , meat . Back for more ? - What are you doing ?
I don 't know , B. What am I doing ? Call Sam . Ask the pro .
What ?
You play with your new friends , and I 'll play with mine .
Ginger , what the hell are you doing ?
You smell yummy . What is that ? Citrus or antiseptic ? I 'm not sure .
Are you crazy ?
- OK , that 's enough . Just let her go . - Shut up . Shut up , shut up .
OK , let 's just chill . Right , Trina ?
Uh , you know what , Trina ?
She is doing your boy , now . I wouldn 't be so quick to get so friendly .
- Stop it , it 's not like that . - I think she 's scared for you , love , huh ?
She 's an asshole . She 's not worth it .
You asked for this !
You picked Sam over me . Whatever happens now , it is your fault !
- This is not you . Just let 's cope . - Oh , with what ? With this kind of shit .
He 's wrong , moron . You can 't fix this !
You don 't know that . Just give me a chance .
What , another one ? God gee , I don 't know , B
see I 'm going way way out there
way way far from where you live , which you pretty much fucking rule .
Oh god , that 's disgusting , you fucking gross , fucking ...
Back !
Don 't touch me , you freaks . You 're both just totally fucked .
Trina , we were just ...
Uh-oh .
Get up !
Get up now !
Henry , what on earth are you doing out there ?
Come on , don 't eat it until we get inside .
Jesus Christ on a bicycle ! What the ... ?
Girls , I told you , no more deaths in the house !
Don 't be mad , it 's for extra credit .
Back to immaculate in ten minutes .
Corn syrup . Dad , d 'you want some ?
Well I better get this meat away .
I 'll do that .
- Mom . - What ?
What do guys want ?
Brigitte , I 'm so glad you asked .
And that 's what men want .
Some of them might seem cool or different , but they 're all pretty much the same .
- Totally . - Thanks for sharing .
Oh , honey , that 's what we 're here for .
Bed time . It 's a school night . Beauty rest .
This is just great .
Yeah , field hockey will suck now .
Get me a screwdriver .
Oh , god !
Way to go .
Here it is : 'Why your daughter dates dummies ? '
I 'm so glad I hung on to this .
- I think they 're up to something . - They 're just being normal teenage girls .
Then why are they suddenly so interested in what you have to say ?
Stay in your own little world , Henry . This one just confuses you .
Shit . Look at all the worms .
Remember when I used to make you eat them just to get in here ?
Shallow grave ? Oh well , seems appropriate .
You dig for a while .
Look ,
no one ever thinks chicks do shit like this .
Trust me , a girl can only be a slut ,
a bitch , a tease , or the virgin next door .
We 'll just coast on how the world works .
Think she 's pretty ?
If I wasn 't here , would you eat her ?
No .
- God , that 'd be like , fucking her . - You can 't go out anymore .
Well I can 't stay in , I 'll go mental .
We 'll make Pam think you 're at school .
We 'll make school think you 're home sick .
Just till there is no doubt about us in this .
Then we blow , as far away from here as possible .
Your attention , please .
Starting immediately certain students will be paged to the office
to assist the police regarding Trina Sinclair 's disappearance .
She is dead , man .
When your name is called , please come to the office .
Is Ginger avoiding me ?
'Cause I 'm feeling pretty good right now .
I just got a few questions for her , like uh ...
I 'm growing a goddamn tail outta my ass ,
and I thought she might have a few tips on how to deal with keeping that quiet !
- Hurting me won 't help . - See ? I 'm up to some whack shit right now .
I 'm way out on the corner of 'Fucked-Up and Evil ' .
You wanna know what I did for fun last night , huh ?
I killed my own freaking dog , OK ? What am I supposed to do about that ?
- You 're gonna be in deep shit . - I 'm right with you on deep shit ,
and I think you know why .
What 's going on here ?
Thanks .
- Ginger , how was school today ? - I don 't know , I didn 't go .
- We had a field trip . - Really ?
I didn 't sign any form for a field trip .
Daddy , will you teach me how to drive tonight ?
Next year . Maybe .
So where did you go ?
- What if next year never comes ? - Ginger .
Mr. Wayne called today .
He wanted to know if you were feeling any better .
When you might be coming back to school .
The police wanna talk to you . Something about a fight with a missing girl ?
- Daddy , may I be excused ? - No , you may not .
- Ginger , wait . - For what , B ?
Oh no , you don 't .
I want to know what 's going on . Right now .
- What are these ? - Monkshood . Brigitte ...
- Where did you get them ? - From a craft store . Now , I want an answer .
Trina Sinclair tried to beat me up , 'cause Jason McCardy liked us better ,
- so Ginger beat her up . That 's all . - That 's all ?
Beating up other girls ? Cutting classes ?
- I 'm very disappointed , Brigitte . - Sorry .
You just do whatever she wants you to . You always have .
I really wish you 'd start thinking more for yourself .
Do you think I should talk to her ?
Check in ?
She thinks it 's cool you let us figure stuff out for ourselves .
Oh ?
Really ?
Well ...
I wondered if that approach was working .
Look what Pamela had .
- What are you doing ? Stop ! - I 'll just take it off .
No !
I killed their pets , B.
And nothing helps except tearing live things to pieces .
I can 't be like this .
This is monkshood .
First thing tomorrow we find out how to use it and we take off .
If you give up now , you leave me here alone . I would never do that to you !
I 'm sorry . I 'm scared .
BCX radio wishes you a happy Halloween ...
B , what the fuck are you doing ?
Hey ... B , let me out !
I have to deal with the cure .
This way , you can 't hurt yourself or anybody else .
Fuck . You fucking sissy little girl . You 're going rat me out ?
Just shut up and wait for me .
You little bitch ! Fuck you ! I hate you !
B , let me out . Come on .
B ?
B !
Let me out !
Holy shit , that 's monkshood . Where the fuck did you get that ?
I don 't know if you smoke it or eat it or what , but I need to try it now .
Well , you got me but
to be sure , I 'd have to say direct route . Inject it .
But see , that 's a bad idea Brigitte , because neither of us know what this stuff does .
It can 't be worse than being road kill .
The dosage will be a guess . I mean ...
It would have to be , there is no way to match for ...
metabolism , bodyweight , there could be side effects .
- You cannot try this alone . - My sister will be there .
Understand you may kill her trying to save her .
What ?
It 's for Ginger , isn 't it ?
Look , worst-case scenario , you put her out of her misery .
Just as long as you 're prepared for that , and I mean sure .
Try to come tonight .
Hey , have you seen Jason ?
Umm ... you got a little ...
You 're going to the greenhouse bash tonight ?
- Erm , yeah . - Good .
I 'm in charge of the prizes . You , too , could be a winner .
Ginger . My office . Now . Alright ?
Help ! Help !
Let me go .
Let me go !
Let him go , McCardy .
Oh yeah , a chick . Excellent .
Come to papa , baby .
Come and get some candy .
I have to go . Uhm ...
I have a class .
Attention please .
Brigitte Fitzgerald , please report to guidance .
Brigitte Fitzerald to guidance .
He wanted to call fucking Pamela , B , and tell her we needed help .
So , I stopped him .
You see how that works ? How I do not betray you ?
I didn 't betray you .
You locked me up .
You need to get this fixed .
Why ? So I can go to jail , for the rest of my life ?
We wait till everyone leaves ,
then we clean this up , somehow .
I think you 've fucked up enough .
Oh my god !
- Henry ? - Oh g ...
What is it ?
Henry , for Pete 's sake . It 's for the girls ' death project .
They 're fake , you big baby .
I 'm gonna find something to clean this up .
Stay here and lock the door .
Oh my god !
Hello , Brigitte .
- Stop it ! - Can I touch your boobies ?
I like little girls .
Leave him alone !
Ginger . Stop ! Stop !
Ginger , fucking stop !
Please stop !
Ginger , stop ! He hasn 't done anything !
I don 't like how he looks at you .
Oh my god !
He found me . Brigitte .
- The mess . I had to ... - Go to hell !
He 's not dead . You 've infected him .
Let me call help for him .
Oh fuck !
Fuck !
You like it .
It feels so ... good , Brigitte .
It 's like touching yourself .
You know every move ... right on the fucking dot .
And after
you see fucking fireworks , supernovas .
I 'm a goddamn force of nature .
I feel like I could do just about anything .
You know we 're almost not even related anymore .
You 're fucked !
You 'd love it . Should come for the ride .
A little scratch . Swap some juice .
We 'll be our own pack , like before . It 's so us , B.
I 'd rather be dead than be what you are .
We have a pact !
Out by sixteen or dead in this scene , but together for fucking ever !
I said I would die for you !
No . You said you 'd die with me . 'Cause you had nothing better to do .
Fuck you too .
You think I wanna go back to being nobody ?
You 're fucked !
Stay the hell out of my way , Brigitte .
And I 'll tell Sam you said hi .
Stop ! Stop !
Where 's your sister ?
County greenhouse .
Get in the van .
All right , Fitz . Wicked costume , baby .
Where is Sam ?
Shit !
Hey .
- Hey Ginger , where is Brigitte ? - She couldn 't make it .
- Yeah , why is that ? - Cramps .
She says hi .
You wanna buy or something ?
Or something .
- Go get your sister . - Mom , I don 't think ...
You 've done a terrible thing .
But
you 're my tiny babies .
It 's one thing if you leave , it 's almost normal ,
but no one is gonna take you from me .
First thing tomorrow I 'll let the house fill up with gas , and I 'll light a match .
What ?
We 'll start fresh . Just us girls . It 'll be fun .
What about dad ?
He 'll just blame me , they all will .
This isn 't your fault , mom .
Yes it is .
Lock the doors , OK ?
- Ginger , come on . - No , you come on .
- What are you doing ? - I know you want to . Everybody does .
Really , what would I be like ?
What would I do ?
- What would I feel like inside ? - Ginger , stop .
- Make me . - Ginger , your sister ...
This is fucked .
Ginger , get off me . Get off me .
Ginger , get off me !
Jerk !
What ? I told you to stop . Oh Jesus .
God , Ginger get up . I 'm sorry .
Get up , Ginger .
You bitch !
You want me ? You want me ?
Stop hurting everybody else and take me . Take me !
I don 't want you ! I don 't even know you !
Brigitte , don 't .
Brigitte , don 't !
You wrecked everything for me that isn 't about you .
No .
Shit .
Now I am you .
I know you are . But what am I ?
We got to go .
B , I can 't . I 'm turning too fast .
- What the hell did you do that for ? - I won 't let you do this , Brigitte .
You both need help .
You fucking idiot !
The cure works .
I had to use it on somebody else , but there is more at the house .
This is the only way I could get her to come back with me .
Oh shit !
What ? How was I supposed to know that ?
Just help me , OK ? Just get her in your truck and drive us home .
Fine , but she rides in the back .
This is nuts , you need a doctor .
Oh !
Jesus .
She could have killed you , Brigitte .
She needs me .
Get home . Cure her , cure me .
And then what ?
Run .
You know you 're kidding yourself .
I 'll be right back . Give me the syringe .
Dad ? Hello ?
Oh shit !
Yeah , I meant to fix that .
- Did she get out ? - Oh god , I hope not .
I can 't see anything .
Pass me that flashlight .
Fuck !
That was your god damn sister !
Oh fuck .
The monkshood 's in there .
Oh , you 're out of your mind .
Not yet .
Be quiet . I gotta get the stuff .
Great .
Fuck ! Where the fuck is she ?
Shh .
- Let 's do this fast . - Hell , yes .
All right , bowls .
Alcohol , alcohol .
Brigitte .
Could I have your lighter ?
I can 't feel my hand .
Jesus Christ .
Oh fuck !
Go ! Go !
- Alcohol . - What ?
- Alcohol ! - Oh shit . Yeah .
Start grinding up the buds .
All right , pour it in .
Easy , easy , easy " -
What was that ?
Shit , keep going . Go , go .
All right , hold this .
- Right , that 's real fucking hygienic . - I doubt it matters .
How about you take this and we blow ?
How about no ?
Then let me do it , you can hardly move .
No !
You can 't do this by yourself .
Let me take the needle , I 'll go into the living room ,
you lead her in , bam we 're done .
- OK . - OK .
- I 'm going . - Be careful .
Sam ?
Ginger ?
I can 't .
I won 't .
The fuck .
Fuck !
Fuck off !
Leave me alone !
Ginger ?
Come on . It 's me .
OK ?
Ginger , please , it 's me !
You want this ?
I 'm not dying in this room with you !
I 'm not dying !